y'all heard me say it before when
reviewing weightlifting belts that
supporting your core is huge when it
comes to lifting heavy weight while the
same can be true when it comes to your
joints when it comes to knee sleeves
they can provide your knees with the
proper support they need as well as
keeping them stable and keeping them as
warm as your favorite blanket I've been
using the gym Reaper's seven millimeter
knee sleeves for quite a while now so
today I'm going to share with you guys
what I found
what's up everybody it's Jake back in
the barbing garage gym and today I've
got a pair of gym Reapers seven
millimeter knee sleeves in full review
but you know before I tell you about
everything you need to know about these
sleeves from the price and the features
as well as some pros and cons and you
know who should or maybe should not buy
these I gotta let you know we've
reviewed a ton of knee sleeves on
barbin.com and if you want to browse our
best list just go ahead and search bar
Bend best knee sleeves and you can find
out for yourself which ones that we like
the best but also you know which ones
are going to suit your needs the best
foreign
so before I dive in on what I like about
these knee sleeves a lot of you may be
asking you know why do I even need to
wear any sleeves well it's actually
pretty simple so knee sleeves are going
to provide your knees with warmth and
compression and this is going to
ultimately increase the amount of blood
flow you have to that part of your body
and it's going to help you with your
Technique allow you to stay more you
know controlled and be more stable while
you're lifting there's also different
types of knee sleeves that you can
purchase so power lifters you know
you're probably going to want to get a
thicker knee sleeve you know it's going
to provide the most amount of stability
you could really ask for a lot of
crossfitters you know you're probably
going to want a thinner pair of knee
sleeves it's going to allow you to be
more mobile but it's still going to
provide you know that part of your body
with an increased amount of blood flow
and keep everything warm you know that
way you're able to lift at your maximum
capacity now with these knee sleeves
some gym Reapers you get a little bit of
Best of Both Worlds so once again
they're seven millimeters thick so
they're going to allow you you know to
get a bunch of support and stability
while you're doing some power lifts like
a squat for example but because of the
Contour design it's going to allow you
to stay mobile enough to use them for
some Olympic lifting and Crossfit
lifting as well okay so let's keep
talking about what I like about these
knee sleeves no I really like how snug
they fit without actually restricting my
movements and that's definitely because
of that Contour design you know a lot of
those power lifting knee sleeves the
seams the stitches are not going to
really allow you to bend your knees too
much right now with these because of
that Contour design you're definitely
going to be able to move pretty freely
and that's really awesome in my opinion
and you know let's be honest you know
our bodies don't always feel the best
when we're going to work out and I gotta
tip my cap to these knee sleeves because
they kind of eliminate that problem
completely they're also approved by the
USPA so if you are in fact a competitor
these are going to be a really solid
option for you to consider you know
during your next meet or even just to
practice with as well so that's really
nice they're made from a high quality
neoprene so they really shouldn't weaken
or tear on you during an extended amount
of period of usage but if you ever
notice anything Jim Reapers actually
tosses in a one-year replacement
guarantee so if there's any
manufacturing defects just send it back
and they'll send you a new pair no
charge whatsoever and they're also
available for a really solid price of
right around 50 bucks and you know you
do in fact get a pair that's not always
the case you know sometimes you got to
spend at least 30 bucks just on one
sleeve so it's a really nice deal right
here
[Music]
okay now with all that good stuff being
said there's still a couple of issues
you might experience with these knee
sleeves but first of all it's kind of
going to depend on you know your style
of lifting so because of the contoured
fit it's going to allow you to have more
Mobility when you're lifting and yeah
that might sound like you know a really
positive thing but a lot of people are
going to prefer a straight knee sleeve
because it actually provides you with
even more stability as you're doing a
deep squat for example and if you're
more interested you know just keeping
your knees warm rather than having a
bunch of support you might not be too
crazy about the seven millimeter
thickness with these sleeves and you
might be interested in some five
millimeter maybe even some three
millimeter sleeves just you know keep
your knees warm while you're working out
and sizing can be a little bit tricky as
well you know they tell you that on the
website so definitely keep that in mind
whenever you measure your knee for your
you know specific sleeves you actually
want to go down one size and what you
measure and that way you know it's a
super tight fit
foreign
now in terms of pricing these seven
millimeter knee sleeves are available
for right around 50 bucks on the Jim
Reaper's website you can also purchase
them from Amazon if you'd rather if
you'd rather do that now these
definitely are not the most expensive
knee sleeves on the market but they're
also not the cheapest so I've seen some
knee sleeves be as expensive as 90 bucks
and I've seen some be as cheap as 15 to
20 bucks now since these fall right in
the middle I think it's a really solid
price you know they're definitely going
to last you longer than that 15 to 20
dollar pair they might even last you as
long as that 90 pair because of you know
the high quality build right here so
considering all that I think they're
definitely worth the money
foreign
okay so let's talk about the build now
and some features with these knee
sleeves from gym Reapers so once again
you know they have a contour design it's
going to allow you to be pretty mobile
when you're working out but they also
provide a lot of support which is
obviously really nice and kind of what
they're designed for now these are
available in three different colors as
you can tell I have the black and white
it's got a little bit of gray mixed in
right here there's also a red and black
pair you can purchase as well as olive
green and black so you know you can
match your Gym gear if you want to and
some nice variety right there for you so
once again these are seven millimeters
thick it's gonna really you know trap
that heat in as well as you know
increase your blood flow now whenever
you go and measure yourself for your
knee sleeves make sure you fully extend
your leg and measure around your kneecap
to get that best fit possible these are
available in five different sizes small
medium large extra large and double XL
and once again gym Reapers lets it be
known on their website that if you do in
fact want a tight fitting sleeve you
actually want to go down one size from
what you actually measure
all right so let's go ahead and do a
quick walk around with these knee
sleeves you know once again these are
made from neoprene seven millimeters
thick they're going to provide you with
that warmth increase the blood flow to
your knees and just overall provide you
with more support when you're working
out now once again you know these are
have a contour design as you can see
right here yes you have stitching in the
back but the stitching on the sides
right here is really going to allow you
to keep your knees pretty mobile when
you're working out and that can be
pretty huge now when it comes to putting
these on you know a lot of people may
not really know the best way and yeah
there's multiple ways you can do it but
personally but I think the best way to
do is just fold this down the top part
Maybe
you know a third of the way maybe half
the way down and just go ahead and slide
this up your leg once you get this
bottom part really where you want it to
be just go ahead and unfold it and then
you're good to go I mean it's pretty
simple it's not going to slide off on
you especially you know if you do it
with Jim Reapers suggests and you go
down one size what you actually measure
that way you get you know a tight fit
now when it comes to cleaning these
you're definitely going to want to do
that from time to time best way to do it
is just toss it in with your regular
laundry and then let them air dry and
this is important every once in a while
that way they keep that tight fit and
you know don't get too loose on you now
when it comes to the gym bag you get
it's pretty simple you know it's just a
normal drawstring bag but this is pretty
cool if you don't have a duffel bag or
anything else you used stash all your
Gym gear in you know this can definitely
serve as that purpose
[Applause]
all right so who should purchase these
knee sleeves from Jim Reapers well if
you are in fact looking for a brand new
pair of knee sleeves that's going to
allow you to be pretty mobile while also
providing you with a good amount of
support I think this is a really good
option for you to consider if you're a
competitor and you're out there looking
for a pair of knee sleeves that are
approved by the USPA well guess what
these definitely are right here so
that's going to be really nice for you
and they're also really competitively
priced so if you're buying on a budget
you know this is going to be really good
for you as well plus you get a sweet
drawstring back so if you're looking for
a new bag well you get the best of both
worlds right here
foreign
[Music]
now when it comes to those people who
might not want to purchase these knee
sleeves my opinion it really just boils
down to two different things let's talk
about the thickness first you know once
again these are seven millimeters thick
that might be too thick for some people
who are just looking for some warmth not
necessarily a ton of compression if
that's you then I'd suggest looking for
some three millimeter even some five
millimeter knee sleeves instead and I
like the Contour design it allows me to
stay pretty mobile while I'm working out
but not everybody wants that so if
that's you you don't really care for the
Contour design I suggest going after
some straight knee sleeves because they
probably are going to provide you with
more support and stability that's about
all I have for you guys today on the gym
Reaper's seven millimeter knee sleeves I
like working out these sleeves
personally you know they keep my knees
warm provide me with more stability they
just overall allow me to be more
confident when I'm lifting some people
might not be too crazy about the Contour
design but if you are in fact looking
for some knee sleeves that provide a
good amount of support don't necessarily
sacrifice Mobility I think these are a
really solid option for you to consider
thanks for watching everybody I hope
this video was really helpful and I was
able to answer any questions you may
have about these knee sleeves as always
stay posted for my next video but for
now you should definitely head over to
barbin.com and you can read more about
this product just search bar Bend Jim
Reaper's knee sleeves review and you'll
find everything that I talked about here
today I'll see y'all next time
tonight
[Music]